wowcher.co.uk 2016-11-20

# Wowcher | Privacy Policy

Effective from 3 October 2016

This privacy policy applies only to this website (the "Site"). If you do not accept this privacy policy, you must not use the Site.

## Collection of Personal Information

We, Wowcher Limited, collect personal information from you (such as name, address, telephone number, email address etc) when you complete registration or enquiry forms, order any products or services, participate in message boards, blogs or any other user generated content facilities or send emails to us. Please do not submit your personal information to us if you do not wish us to collect it.

## Use of Cookies

In addition to personal information you provide, we may also collect information about you automatically when you visit the Site or access content in our electronic communications with you. 

The collection of information may involve the use of cookies and web beacons. A web beacon is a small graphic image placed on a web page that is designed to allow us to monitor traffic on the Site or within electronic communications. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your computer's hard drive by your browser. Cookies allow us to identify your computer and find out details about your visit and browsing habits so that we can offer you a more personalised experience and manage, monitor and improve services. 

Most internet browsers accept cookies automatically, but usually you can alter the settings of your browser to erase cookies or prevent automatic acceptance if you prefer. If you choose not to receive our cookies, you may not be able to use some of the core features of the Site. 

The information collected by cookies and web beacons is not tied to your contact details (such as your name or email address), it only includes general information about your computer settings, your connection to the internet e.g. operating system and platform, IP address, your browsing patterns and timings of browsing on the Site and geographical location. 

Display advertising on the Site is provided by our advertising partners. Our advertising partners will serve advertisements that they believe are most likely to be of interest to you, based on information about your visit to the Site and other websites (this information does not include your name, street address, email address or telephone number). For more information about this type of online behavioural advertising please visit [ www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/). 

For more detail on our cookies, and on trusted 3rd party companies using cookies on our Site [click here](http://www.wowcher.co.uk/cookies.html). One of the third party cookies on our site is provided by Criteo. The purpose of Criteo's service is to find visitors who also visit the websites of other companies on the Criteo network and serve these visitors personalized ads or where we or the other company has consent from the visitor, send personalized emails. Criteo uses cookies to single out visitors and then personalize ads based on their browsing experience. To learn more or opt out of Criteo [click here](http://privacy.criteoemail.com/gb/index.html). 

You can learn more about cookies and how to reject cookies using different types of browser by visiting [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/). 

Separate tools are also available for managing local shared objects or 'Flash cookies' from the [Adobe website ](http://www.adobe.com/). These cookies may be used to manage the effective delivery of services using video or other flash related content. 

## Use of Your Information

By using this Site, you agree that we may collect, hold, process and use your information (including personal information) for the purpose of providing you with the Site services and developing our business which includes (without limitation):

  * personalising your visits to the Site and developing the design and style of the Site to improve the services provided to you;
  * contacting you if you have not finalised your order to follow up on your abandoned shopping cart and/or to see if there was a problem with your use of the Site;
  * informing you about the latest changes to the Site, products, services or promotional offers that you might find interesting;
  * customer service and support;
  * communicating (and personalising such communication) with you;
  * enabling you to share our content with others e.g. using an 'Email a friend' or 'Share this' functionality;
  * conducting market research; and/or
  * carrying out technical and statistical analysis to measure the performance of our services and the Site.

## Sharing Your Personal Information

We may share information about you with suppliers that we engage to help us provide certain services and/or functionality e.g online payment processing. We will use reasonable endeavours to control and be responsible for the use of your information by such suppliers. Furthermore, by using the Site, you consent to the transfer of your personal information outside of the European Economic Area (which may not provide the same protection for such information as the European Economic Area provides) in the event that the processing of your information involves such a transfer.

We may disclose your information (including personal information) throughout our company (including in relation to other brands which are owned by Wowcher Limited) and to other companies within our group which includes LivingSocial Europe Limited and may use and share with those companies information that we learn from your interactions with us and from other companies in our group.

Subject to your consent, your personal information may be used by us and/or other companies within our group to contact you by email, fax, telephone, SMS and/or post with information and offers on products/services provided by us and/or other companies within the group. 

Subject to your consent, we may supply personal information about you to selected third parties so that they may contact you with information and offers which may be of interest to you.

We reserve the right to disclose your personal information to comply with applicable laws and government or regulatory bodies' lawful requests for information. 

We may transfer, sell or assign any of the information described in this policy to third parties as a result of a sale, merger, consolidation, change of control, transfer of assets or reorganisation of our business.

## Keeping Your Personal Information Secure

We take the security of your personal information very seriously and have appropriate physical, technical and administrative procedures in place to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure as required by law in England.

## Accessing Your Personal Information

If you wish to review or receive copies of the personal information we hold about you, change your marketing preferences or have any other queries about this privacy policy, please write to us (including full details of your request) at the following address:

Privacy Team  
Wowcher Towers  
Northcliffe House  
Meadow Road  
Derby  
DE1 2BH  
0203 699 5024

We may charge a small administration fee (not exceeding the maximum permitted by law in England or Ireland as applicable) in relation to fulfilling a request for access to personal information.

## Unsubscribing from emails

If you wish to unsubscribe from emails from the Site, please click on the unsubscribe link in your email.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

If we change this privacy policy, we will post the revised privacy policy here with an updated effective date. If we make significant changes to the privacy policy, we may also notify you by other means such as sending an email or posting a notice on our home page.
